Software Engineer

MADDALA MANIKANTA

EXPERIENCE

GGK Tech

Software Engineer | Since June 2018

Worked as full stack web developer on projects based on PHP and it's MVC frameworks such as Yii2 and Joomla. I have also worked on projects using Angular/React and Node.js

Freelance

Web Developer | September 2017 - May 2018

Worked on few freelance projects using PHP which include developing web applications, writing wordpress themes and plugins etc.,

Osmosys software solutions

Associate Software Engineer | September 2016 - August 2017

Worked as full stack web developer on projects based on PHP and it's MVC frameworks such as CakePHP and writing wordpress themes and plugin development. Find out more here: https://manikantalse.github.io/

EDUCATION

Computer science degree from Sreyas Institute of Engineering and Technology(JNTUH), Hyderabad, Telangana[2012-2016].

Bachelor of Technology | September 2012 - May 2016

SKILLS

Portfolio website: https://manikantalse.github.io/

HTML5

PHP

Node.js

- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Angular
- React

About me

I'm M. Manikanta L.S.E., a self taught web deveopler from Hyderabad, India. I have 1 year of industrial experience in both front-end and back-end development. I am passionate about creating Happy Digital Interactions for people. I'm currently available for projects small or large.